Ah, it wasn't me, Your Majesty.
It was those two young eunuchs.
I will kill them for Your Majesty.
Aunt.
The people you planted are getting more and more insolent.
Now is not the time to kill this dog.
Alright.
Sun Liang failed to manage his subordinates properly.
He will be fined half a year's salary.
Yes.
I'll go kill them right now.
Get out of here!
Go.
Useless.
Ayan, don't be afraid. It's okay.
How can a mere eunuch like you protect him?
His Majesty gave the young prince the largest
and best palace in the palace.
They will still bully him.
Knowing it was Eunuch Sun,
but not killing him on the spot.
Does Si Xingxuan have some unspeakable difficulties?
It seems I have to think of a way.
The royal doctor said the young prince was poisoned.
The fever will go down
only when the toxin is completely cleared from the body.
How dare he bully Ayan like this.
I am not dead yet.
Your Majesty.
I hope you will protect Ayan well in the future.
I don't mean anything else.
Just a reminder.
Take good care of Ayan.
I feel His Majesty actually cares a lot about the little prince.
What's the use of caring?
Now that the little prince is sick,
he doesn't even dare to visit often.
If he visits too much,
it will become his weakness.
The Grand Princess is no good.
But at that time,
why did you lie to me
and say that Si Xingxuan was a tyrant?
You sneaked into the palace in a wooden barrel.
How could I trust you?
All right.
Uh, I have another question.
Why doesn't His Majesty dare to touch Eunuch Sun
when he is the Emperor?
Because he is the Grand Princess's man.
Once he is killed,
the Grand Princess will take vicious revenge on the little prince.
That woman is just too crazy.
What a lunatic.
His Majesty is in a bad mood.
I'll go check on him.
After so long,
there's finally some hope.
Cang Yue,
please don't let me down.
Come and sit.
I told you to come and sit.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
You saw it yourself today.
In this deep palace,
danger lurks everywhere.
You should leave immediately.
I am not afraid of being dragged into trouble.
I just want to know
the truth behind the massacre of the Yueying Tribe.
I promise you
I will help you find the truth.
You don't believe me.
That's true.
I can't even deal with a eunuch like Sun Liang.
Who says you can't?
Evil will be punished by evil.
So I won't leave the palace.
But from what I see,
evil people in this deep palace
can thrive.
Greedy people always have weaknesses.
I don't want to leave the palace.
I just want to go to the riverbank with Your Majesty
and fish in the clear water together.
Experiencer's character task goal is 40% complete.
Does Your Majesty know how to fish?
Fishing?
Lady Cangyue.
About yesterday,
I never intended to kill you.
Really?
Why do I feel
it's because you were too slow?
No, no, no.
Every maid His Majesty favors
has to go through this process with me.
You have passed this process.
Anything else?
No, nothing.
Then things between us
are settled.
We'll be at peace.
Mm.
The show has just begun. Just wait.
Hey, did you know?
His Majesty is exclusively favoring a maid now.
It's that Cangyue.
She has completely captivated His Majesty.
Why still call her a maid?
Next time we see her, we'll have to call her Consort.
We are all human, but with different fates.
We are all maids.
Why does she get His Majesty's exclusive favor?
My figure isn't bad either.
Let's get back to work.
Head Eunuch Sun will punish us if he catches us.
You have been paying your respects quite frequently lately.
My father and I are where we are today
all thanks to Aunt's support.
I am truly grateful,
so naturally I care about you, Princess.
Yes, I have always been thinking of you.
I think
you fail to capture His Majesty's heart
and have nothing better to do.
Having been concubines for so long,
have any of you ever served him in bed?
What use are you?
Every one of you holds the title of concubine.
Yet you can't even capture the Emperor's heart.
You are worse than a lowly palace maid.
I don't need to teach you
what to do, do I?
- You may leave.
- Yes.
At such an important occasion,
that little palace maid is nowhere to be seen.
Has she fallen out of favor?
I thought a real seductress had appeared
and stolen His Majesty's heart.
It seems Cangyue is nothing special after all.
His Majesty is hosting a banquet today.
He must miss us.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, I...
If your eyes are uncomfortable,
summon the imperial physician to take a look.
Your Majesty, you haven't visited me for a long time.
I have face blindness.
I can't see.
Your Majesty, in my palace...
I told you not to talk nonsense.
Your Majesty,
I have the best pre-Qingming Longjing tea in my palace.
I would like you to taste it.
What's so good about your tea?
Your Majesty, I have a silver heron.
It's so cute.
Come to my place to see it.
What's the rush?
If His Majesty goes anywhere, he will come to me.
Your Majesty,
it's time to flip the name tag.
Consort Yu.
Ah, it's me.
Your Majesty, I...
Get out.
Ah.
I told you to get out.
Hmph. I don't care.
I am staying right here.
Hmph.
You... shut up.
Consort Hua.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
You get out too.
If she won't get out,
neither will I.
Your Majesty.